(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T22:48:54.816861",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I'm a country girl,
but you're a super city boy.
I'm a natural girl,
but you're prince for me.
Everyday wondering how I become your girl.
Everynight I'm feeling your body in my dreams.
I can't sleep at all,
hello, morning sun.
My love, my crush, wanna tell you my feeling.
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you one for you
Everytime,
everywhere,
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke
I'm a natural girl,
but you're prince for me.
I'm a country girl,
but you're a super city boy.
Everyday wondering how I become your girl.
Every night, I'm feeling your body in my dreams.
I can't sleep at all,
hello, morning sun.
My love, my crush, wanna tell you my feeling.
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now,
I wanna dance with you more.
Right now, I want you one for you.
Everytime,
everywhere,
I will surely get your honest love.
Daisuke
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now,
I wanna dance with you more.
Right now, I want you one for you.
Everytime,
everywhere,
I will surely get your honest love.
Daisuke
Let's go!
1, 2, 3, let's go!
Lost hope in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads I ignored before, you left me wanting more
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon lights fly by, is it fake or reality?
Not sure of much but know I'm ready
Soaring these streets, make me complete
Full throttle, come give me your all
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
Till the sun's up
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all ok
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end
But we'll keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated love
One, two, three, let's go!
Took a bet on love, it's better than I coulda dreamed
Look at what we've done, we're too extreme
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing
The track we're on might crash, oh what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues
Race through the night, my guiding light
Sparkling, I'm right here with you
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
Till the sun's up
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated love
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, speed up, let's make it new
Love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on going until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up again
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up and begin
Carbonated love
HiRyS! It's IRyS from hololive English -Promise-!
Look at who we have here. Aren't they so cute? かわいいっすね、こいつら。
Look at who we have here. Aren't they so cute? Aren't they cute, these guys?
ねー、頑張ってね、一緒に踊っていただいたんで。うい、嬉しい！
Yeah, thank you for working hard and dancing together with me. Yay, I'm so happy!
And, before we get into all sorts of things, first off...
Please use the hashtag #IRySBDay2026...
Ah, this way! #IRySBDay2026!
こちらのハッシュタグぜひぜひツイートしてくださいね、感想など。
Please be sure to tweet your impressions using this hashtag.
If you have anything you want to talk about this live, please use the hashtag. See, these GuyRyS will definitely get on their phones later on too to tweet with the hashtag.
And, have you guys noticed something different?
なんか、なんかアイリスいつもの見た目と違うでしょ？
Like, IRyS looks a bit different than usual, right?
どう？ Race queen!
How is it? Race queen!
あ、興奮してる！ They look very excited! Yeah, all... they're going mad, yes!
Ah, they're excited! They look very excited! Yeah, all... they're going mad, yes!
それくらい、素晴らしいでしょ？
Isn't it that wonderful?
Finally, the Race Queen outfit is real! Yeah!
ね、いいね。ありがとうございます。サクラじゃないよ！
Right, isn't it great? Thank you very much. They're not paid audience members!
All righty then, first off though, let's get started with introducing the merch, the goods!
Here is the lineup this time.
Introducing merch pretty early on this time. It's supposed to pop out...
この辺かな？
Around here maybe?
はい！ グッズはこちらになります！
Here! The merch is right here!
Yes, the IRyS Birthday Celebration 2026! アイリス生誕... えーっと、誕生日記念2026年！
Yes, the IRyS Birthday Celebration 2026! IRyS's birthday... um, Birthday Celebration 2026!
All right, let me introduce the goods one by one. First off, there's this one.
GuyRyS も喜んでるね！ Yes, first up we have the Acrylic Diorama Stand.
The GuyRyS are happy too! Yes, first up we have the Acrylic Diorama Stand.
Acrylic Diorama StandRyS!
Illustration is by... the very beautiful...
Inudog Bisuke-sensei! こちらの衣装もビスケ先生なんですよー
Inudog Bisuke-sensei! This outfit was also drawn by Bisuke-sensei!
うふふ、あっ
Hehe, ah!
The diorama stand features IRyS in her race queen outfit,
perfectly capturing the atmosphere of this 3D live stage! Yes!
みんなも買おうねー！ イエーイ！
Everyone, make sure to buy one too! Yay!
はい！ And then the second one is this one! Yes!
Alright! And then the second one is this one! Yes!
The ChibiIRyS Tote Bag! It's so cute!
Illustration on the tote bag is by LIEN-sensei!
いつも LIEN-sensei ありがとう！ Thank you so much LIEN all the time!
Thank you always LIEN-sensei! Thank you so much LIEN all the time!
It's so cute, I love ChibiIRyS!
This tote features the mini IRyS in her casual outfit!
Yes, drawn by LIEN-sensei, so cute!
LIEN先生に書いてもらったカジュアルアイリスのチビになってます！ 可愛いトート！
It's a cute tote featuring chibi casual IRyS drawn by LIEN-sensei!
ぜひ普段使いしてください！ お出かけで使ってね！ はい！
Please use it every day! Use it when you go out! Yes!
Please use it when you go shopping or whatnot!
And with this simple design, it's perfect for everyday use!
You can pair it with other merch that I'll be introducing right after this, so show off your IRyS pride! Yay!
この後に紹介するグッズとも合わせて使えるんで、楽しみにしててね！ はい！
You can pair it with the merch I'll introduce after this, so look forward to it! Alright!
えーっと、And then the third one...
Umm, and then the third one...
...is The Race QueenIRyS Keychain!
こちらの素晴らしい衣装のキーホルダーになってます！ かわいいやろー？
It's a keychain of this wonderful outfit! Isn't it cute?
あ、欲しいの？ Oh, you guys want it already? They want it already!
Oh, you want it? Oh, you guys want it already? They want it already!
まだダメー！ こっからだよー！ 注文するよね？ You guys are going to buy it, right?
Not yet! It starts from here! You'll order it, right? You guys are going to buy it, right?
Yeah! Yeah! 1セットでは終わらないよね？
Yeah! Yeah! You won't stop at just one set, right?
うん！ うん！ もう爆買いしてくれるそうです！ はい！
Yup! Yup! Looks like they're going to buy in bulk! Yes!
Um, this is the new plushie featuring my new outfit!
新衣装のアイリスがぬいぐるみキーホルダーになっちゃったよー！
IRyS in her new outfit became a plushie keychain!
It's definitely cute on its own, but you can also carry it with its face peeking out from the outer pocket of the tote bag!
ぜひトートバッグの中にぽんと入れちゃって、一緒にお出かけしてねー！
Please pop it inside the tote bag and go out together!
はい！ And then the last one is The YabaiRyS Pouch!
Alright! And then the last one is The YabaiRyS Pouch!
みんなの大好きなヤバイリスだよー！
It's everyone's beloved YabaiRyS!
何を考えてるんでしょう？ I wonder what she's thinking with that face of hers, yes!
What is she thinking? I wonder what she's thinking with that face of hers, yes!
YabaiRyS is back again! This face pouch with its high-impact design!
Yes, it's high impact! Can also be attached to the bag handle!
そう、先ほど紹介したトートバッグの取っ手にぽんと付けるととっても可愛いよ！
Yes, if you attach it to the handle of the tote bag I introduced earlier, it's super cute!
Yes, you can use it with the tote bag, just put it on the tote bag and it'll be a perfect set!
トートとぬい and the pouch as a three-piece set, you can show off your IRyS love all around the world!
The tote, plushie, and pouch as a three-piece set, you can show off your IRyS love all around the world!
あ、ちなみに This is a pouch, by the way. Just clarifying.
Ah, by the way... This is a pouch, by the way. Just clarifying.
これはポーチになってます！ So you can zip it open and put things in it, tiny things in it! Yay!
This is a pouch! So you can zip it open and put things in it, tiny things in it! Yay!
Okay, and then here are the full set bonuses!
Yes! The postcard!
Illustration is the same illustration from Bisuke-sensei for the acrylic stand...
犬白ビスケ先生の素晴らしいイラストをこちらのポストカードでも使ってます！
...and Inudog Bisuke-sensei's wonderful illustration is used on this postcard too!
The limited edition features a handwritten message!
Yes! 数量限定版は直筆メッセージ！ and 箔押し複製サイン入り...
Yes! The limited quantity edition comes with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped signature...
あ、箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードです！
Ah, a postcard with a foil-stamped duplicated signature!
なのでメッセージは直筆、直筆はメッセージの方です！ はい！
So the message is handwritten, the handwritten part is the message! Yes!
So, you guys 数量限定買おうね！
So, you guys buy the limited edition, okay?
Yeah, yeah, I want you guys to be as hyped as them! Yeah!
The standard version comes with a foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message as well!
通常版も勿論あるんで、箔押し複製サイン and メッセージ入りポストカードになってます！
Of course there's a standard edition too, with a foil-stamped signature and message postcard!
So you can get both! 限定版も通常版もぜひゲットしてね！
So you can get both! Make sure to get both the limited and standard editions!
Yeah!
みんな可愛いなー！ You guys are so cute! Ah...
Everyone's so cute! You guys are so cute! Ah...
Ah, they're so cute, look at how big their heads are! 頭でかいね！
Ah, they're so cute, look at how big their heads are! Their heads are huge!
あ、刺される！ あ、痛いよ、痛い！ 痛い、痛いよ！
Ah, I'm getting poked! Ah, it hurts! It hurts, it hurts!
もう、君たちはしょうがないな！
Gosh, you guys are hopeless!
There are plenty more announcements coming up!
Yeah, if you guys thought I'm already introducing merch, there's a lot of other things coming up!
この後もね、色んな大きな告知があるんで、ぜひ最後まで観ててくだいさいね！
There are lots of big announcements coming up after this too, so please stay tuned until the end!
楽しみにしててね！ There's still big announcements after this, so stay tuned!
Look forward to it! There's still big announcements after this, so stay tuned!
イエーイ！ じゃ、続きやるぞー！ Let's go on with the live!
Yay! Alright, let me continue! Let's go on with the live!
まるでこの世界で 2人だけみたいだね
It's as if it's just the two of us in this world, isn't it?
なんて少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
I just had a little dream like that...
爪先に月明かり 花束の香り 指に触れる指
Moonlight on my toes, the scent of a bouquet, a finger touching my finger.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ 何もかも忘れて
Goodbye, I have to go now, forgetting everything...
硝子の上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot across the glass,
痛むごとに 血が流れて落ちていく
with every stab of pain, blood flows and falls.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って 会いにきて
Please, follow those red footprints and come see me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusty pool,
靴箱の中 隠したりんご
an apple hidden inside the shoe locker,
萎びた君の肌に残る傷痕
scars left on your withered skin,
犬のように泳いだ迷子
a lost child who swam like a dog.
どこにいるの (ここにいるよ)
Where are you? (I'm here.)
何をしているの (ずっと見てるよ)
What are you doing? (I've been watching you.)
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
側にいてよ 遊びに行こうよ
Stay by my side, let's go play.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
硝子の上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot across the glass,
痛むごとに 血が流れて落ちていく
with every stab of pain, blood flows and falls.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いにきて
Come see me.
まるでこの世界で 2人だけみたいだね
It's as if it's just the two of us in this world, isn't it?
なんて少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
I just had a little dream like that...
[曲名: Gaze on Me!]
[Song: Gaze on Me!]
揺らせ一秒 駆けたら Summer girls
Shake it for a second, sprint and we're summer girls!
夢への道はストレート
The path to our dreams is straight ahead!
視線 誰にも譲れない
Our eyes won't give way to anyone!
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
Surely, a fantastic time is about to start!
(La la la la la la... ゴールは Spot light)
(La la la la la la... The goal is the spotlight)
(La la la la la la... I'm the heroine)
(La la la la la la... キミを頂戴)
(La la la la la la... I want you)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(きっと始まる Fantastic time)
(Surely, a fantastic time is about to start)
みんな準備はいいですか？ Burning
Is everyone ready? Burning!
うなずいて 陽炎も Heat up
Nod along, even the heat haze is heating up!
どうしよう 上昇 アガる空気
What should we do? The vibe keeps rising higher!
Let's go! 太陽 燃えて 最高 Mate
Let's go! The burning sun is the best, mate!
負けられない 興奮もハートも
I can't lose, both my excitement and heart
駆け引きは No no
No mind games, no no!
ゲート 開いたなら
Once the gate opens
一瞬のドラマ
It's a drama of a single moment
走れ 夏の方へ
Run towards summer!
揺らせ 一秒 賭けたら Summer girls
Shake it, bet a single second, summer girls!
夢への道は ストレート
The path to our dreams is straight
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't yield anyone's gaze
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! It'll surely be an exciting, fantastic time!
ゴールは Spotlight
The goal is the spotlight
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴 Please, Gaze on Me! きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time
Give me your heart! Please, Gaze on Me! It'll surely be an exciting, fantastic time!
絶対 最上 掴みたい Feeling
I want to grab that absolute top feeling
全身全霊 めぐるから Get high!
Soaring high with all my body and soul!
テンション 高揚 欲しいもので
Tension rising with everything I desire
今 Ride on time 乗って It's show time
Now ride on time, hop on, it's showtime!
Peak 迎えるとき
When reaching the peak
遠慮はいらない せめぎあい Oh oh
No need to hold back in this clash, oh oh
Spark 汗とプライド ジレた運命
Spark, sweat and pride, impatient fate
連れて 夏の方へ
Take me towards summer
挑む世界は 魅惑の Sunlight floor
The world we challenge is an alluring sunlight floor
天井知らずの ボルテージ
Voltage with no ceiling limit
火照る季節を モノにして
Making this burning season our own
Please, Gaze on Me! クラリさせたい Exciting time
Please, Gaze on Me! I want to make your head spin in this exciting time
ゴールは Spotlight
The goal is the spotlight
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴 Please, Gaze on Me! クラリさせたい Exciting time
Give me your heart! Please, Gaze on Me! I want to make your head spin in this exciting time
関係ないような 私だって 真夏 駆け出せたら Venus
Even if I seem unrelated, if I dash into midsummer, I'm Venus
アツくなれば 一歩で Change & Happy
When it gets hot, one step brings Change & Happy
眩しすぎる今日を 踊るように 手にしよう ( さぁ Here we go! )
Let me grab this dazzling today like dancing! (Come on, here we go!)
ビートは 止まらない
The beat won't stop!
Keep 思うままに 身を預けて 灼熱
Keep surrendering yourself as you wish in the scorching heat
Go go Warp 本能のリズム 打ち鳴らして
Go go Warp! Beat out the rhythm of instinct!
走れ 夏の方へ 揺らせ 一秒 賭けたら Summer girls
Run towards summer! Shake it, bet a single second, summer girls!
夢への道は ストレート 視線 誰にも 譲れない
The path to our dreams is straight, I won't yield anyone's gaze
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと始まる Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is surely starting
I'm the heroine キミを頂戴
I'm the heroine, give me your heart!
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと始まる Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is surely starting
愛♡スクリーム！
Love♡Scream!
教えて！もっと あなたの事
Tell me! More about you
Tell me more more more, Tell me more more more
聞かせて！もっと あなたの声
Let me hear! More of your voice
Let me hear more more more, Let me hear more more more
こんなドキドキ もう抑えきれない
This pounding heart can't be held back anymore
All I need you, oh, All I need you
友達は卒業 運命の私 見つけて欲しいの
Graduating from being friends, I'm your destiny, I want you to find me
One! 勇気を出して
One! Muster your courage
Two! 見つめる作戦
Two! The staring strategy
Three! 瞳と目が合えば Fall
Three! When our eyes lock, we fall
止められない
It can't be stopped!
Yeah yeah yeah この恋 この愛で Melt melt 溶けちゃうよ
Yeah yeah yeah, melting away from this love, this affection
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling
届け！大好き！
Reach out! I love you!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム 叫びましょ
Love, scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム 叫びましょ
Love, scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミント！
Mint chocolate!
より摩亜多...
More than that...
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
IRySちゃん！
IRyS-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレイバーよりもあ・な・た♡
More than strawberry flavor, I like y-o-u♡
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりもあ・な・た
More than cookies & cream, I like y-o-u
みんな！
Everyone!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
モチロン大好き
Of course I love
AiScReam
止められない YEAH YEAH YEAH
Can't stop, YEAH YEAH YEAH
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this affection
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよ
MELT MELTY, I'm melting
ねぇ？ ねぇ？ ねぇ？
Hey? Hey? Hey?
気づいて my darling
Notice me, my darling
届け！ 大好き！
Reach them! I love you!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Ai Love, Scre~am SCREAM, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice Cream!
OK！
OK!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Ai Love, Scre~am SCREAM, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice Cream!
―おねがい見つけて “my darling”―
- Please find me, "my darling" -
―おねがい気づいて “my darling”―
- Please notice me, "my darling" -
One 勇気を出して
One, muster up your courage
Two 近づく作戦
Two, the approaching operation
Three 手と手が触れて
Three, hands touching
Four Fall
止められない YEAH YEAH YEAH
Can't stop, YEAH YEAH YEAH
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this affection
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよ
MELT MELTY, I'm melting
ねぇ？ ねぇ？ ねぇ？
Hey? Hey? Hey?
気づいて my darling
Notice me, my darling
それは！ アナタ！
That is! You!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Ai Love, Scre~am SCREAM, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice Cream!
OK！
OK!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Ai Love, Scre~am SCREAM, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice Cream!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Ai Love, Scre~am SCREAM, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice Cream!
OK！
OK!
アイ愛、スクリ〜ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Ai Love, Scre~am SCREAM, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice Cream!
La la la la la la love love...
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know you're shedding tears all alone, I know.
ビクンビクン震えてさ 声もダダ漏れなんだわ
Trembling and twitching, your voice is leaking right out.
正直に言っちゃえば バレてるんだし
Honestly speaking, it's already obvious.
言っちゃえば 聞いてんの？
Speaking of which, are you listening?
普通普通 平気だよ みんなはわかってないだけ ウツ〜
Normal, normal, it's fine. Others just don't understand, so blue~
もしもーし
Hello~?
ねぇ 大丈夫？
Hey, are you okay?
んー、心配だから今からそっち行くね
Hmm, I'm worried, so I'm heading over to your place now.
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know you're shedding tears all alone, I know.
グスングスン凹んでさ 弱音吐くのいいんじゃない？
Sniffling and feeling down, isn't it fine to show weakness?
朝が来るまで一緒トーク
We'll talk together until morning comes,
もっと泣いたって
even if you cry even more,
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept you no matter how many times.
もう我慢しないでいっぱい吐いてね
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out.
ん〜〜〜わ！ お願いきみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you.
慰めさせて ベストフレンド
Let me comfort you, best friend.
愛の才能で
With the talent of love.
泣いてくれるかい？ きみの辛い 抱きしめたい ねぇいいでしょ？
Will you cry for me? I want to embrace your pain, hey, is it okay?
分け合って 乗り越えたいん だっだっだってば
I want to share it and overcome it, I'm telling you!
ん〜〜〜わ！ お願いきみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you.
笑い飛ばして ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプ 最高で
Laugh it off, hop, step, jump, to the best extent.
分けてくれるかい？ きみに重い 暗い重い ねぇいいでしょ？
Will you share with me? It's heavy on you, dark and heavy, hey, is it okay?
寄り添って 救いたいん だっだっだってば
I want to stay close and save you, I'm telling you!
見たい見たい見たい... の君の中
I want to see, want to see... inside of you.
見たい見たい見たい... 見えー！
I want to see, want to see... Can't see~!
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり悔しがってんの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know you're feeling frustrated all alone, I know.
グスングスン終わるまで きみを決して諦めない
Sniffling, until it ends, I will never give up on you.
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみはできる子 知ってるよ
Hey, I know you're a capable person, I know.
つらい時は 弱いくらいでちょうどいい あたしきみの味方だよ
When it's tough, being a bit weak is just right, I'm on your side.
ん〜〜〜わ！ お願いきみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you.
名前を呼んでよ いつだって 会いに参上
Call my name, anytime I'll come to see you.
きみはひとりかい？ それは違う ひとりじゃない もういいでしょ？
Are you alone? That's wrong, you're not alone, isn't it fine now?
ソロプレイはお仕舞いなん だっだっだってば
Solo play is over, I'm telling you!
きみがどんなときも あたし側にいるわ
No matter when, I'll be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ そうよ怖くないのよ
I'm always watching over you, yes, it's not scary.
ん〜〜〜わ！ お願いきみが欲しいの 慰めさせて...
Mwah! Please, I want you, let me comfort you...
慰めさせてベストフレンド 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, best friend, with the talent of love
泣いてくれるかい？ 君のツライ 抱きしめたいねぇ いいでしょう？
Will you cry for me? I want to hug your pain, hey, isn't that okay?
分け合って 乗り越えたいん だっだっだっていや
I want to share and overcome it, but...
お願い君が欲しいの 笑い飛ばしてホップステップジャンプ最高ゼン
Please, I want you! Laugh it off, hop step jump, the best!
分けてくれるかい？ 君の重い 暗い想い 覗きたい
Will you share with me? I want to peek into your heavy, dark feelings
吸い取って救いたいん だっだっだっていや
I want to absorb and save you, but...
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ 君が1人で涙流してるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're shedding tears all alone
くすんくすん 凹んでさ 弱音吐くのっていいんじゃない？
Sniffling and feeling down... Isn't it okay to show weakness?
ずっと一緒 泣いたって 何度だって受け止めてあげる
Together forever, even if you cry, I'll accept you again and again
もう立ち止まらないで 助けてって言ってよ
Don't hesitate anymore, ask for help!
(Go beat crazy!)
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Beat beat baby, music gets you crazy, shock me tonight
Fun fun baby, dancin' feelin' hazy, shake out of sight
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance, no lovely dovey romance, if you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round, I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go, go, go beat crazy!
Step into the dance, get into the groove, and let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go, go, go beat crazy!
Step into the dance, get into the groove, and let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Boom boom baby, come and shake your booty, dig it tonight
Go go baby, show me that you're ready, get satisfied
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance, no lovely dovey romance, if you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round, I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go, go, go beat crazy!
Step into the dance, get into the groove, and let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go, go, go beat crazy!
Step into the dance, get into the groove, and let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Beat beat baby (Beat beat baby)
Fun fun baby (Go beat crazy!)
Boom boom baby (Boom boom baby)
Go go baby (Go beat crazy!)
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go
Everybody dance, everybody groove, everybody go, go, go beat crazy!
Step into the dance, get into the groove, and let the party go, go beat crazy!
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go, go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go, go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Are you ready?
Everybody make some noise
誰も真似できやしないの
Nobody can imitate this
Starのguidance
Star guidance
カリスマ
Charisma
バズりまくり
Going super viral
常にTacticalに
Always tactical
カリスマ
Charisma
Haterたちにご提案
Here's a proposal for the haters
ディスるより Do what you love
Instead of dissing, do what you love
カリスマ
Charisma
朝から晩まで Ring a ring a ling
From morning to night, ring a ring a ling
勝ちや負け気にするの論外
Winning or losing? Caring about that is out of the question
「ミスるの問題」
"Making a mistake is the problem"
とか言ってるのが大問題
Saying things like that is the real big problem
Alright 自分が一番正解
Alright, I am the ultimate right answer
Everyone 必ず信念を
Everyone, always stick to your convictions
貫く
and carry them through
We are! We are!
No. 1
カリスマックス
Charismax
最強のマインド
The ultimate mindset
カリスマックス
Charismax
時代塗り替える
Rewriting the era
カリスマックス
Charismax
世界が驚く
Astonishing the world
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy man
Every last one of us is a crazy crazy man
常識壊してゆく
Shattering common sense
カリスマックス
Charismax
まるで人生は Stage みたいだ
It's like life is a stage
皆が役者
Everyone is an actor
カリスマ
Charisma
何でもできる
You can do anything
そう 君は何でもできる
That's right, you can do anything
カリスマ
Charisma
Wannabeたちにご提案
Here's a proposal for the wannabes
今すぐに Do what you want
Right now, do what you want
カリスマ
Charisma
世界に響かす Ding a ding a ling
Resonating across the world, ding a ding a ling
空気は読むより変えてく Style
Changing the vibe rather than reading the room, that's my style
はみ出す天才
A standout genius
てか愛想笑いなんてしない
Besides, I don't do fake smiles
Alright 答えは明快
Alright, the answer is crystal clear
Everyone 必ず信念を
Everyone, always stick to your convictions
貫く
and carry them through
We are! We are!
No. 1
カリスマックス
Charismax
才能解き放つ
Unleashing talent
カリスマックス
Charismax
進化をし続ける
Continuously evolving
カリスマックス
Charismax
限界超えてゆく
Going beyond the limits
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy woman
Every last one of us is a crazy crazy woman
Everyone
必ず信念を
always stick to your convictions
貫く We are! We are!
and carry them through, We are! We are!
No. 1
カリスマックス
Charismax
最強のマインド
The ultimate mindset
カリスマックス
Charismax
時代塗り替える
Rewriting the era
カリスマックス
Charismax
世界が驚く
Astonishing the world
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy man
Every last one of us is a crazy crazy man
カリスマックス
Charismax
才能解き放つ
Unleashing talent
カリスマックス
Charismax
進化をし続ける
Continuously evolving
カリスマックス
Charismax
限界超えてゆく
Going beyond the limits
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy woman
Every last one of us is a crazy crazy woman
常識壊してゆく カリスマックス
Shattering common sense, Charismax
Yeah
Aha!
Can I get get get get all your attention?
I bet you don't know me yet
君の奥底まで 穿つ目線で
Piercing straight into the depths of your heart with my gaze,
溢れる様 IQ ammo 獲る天下
overflowing with IQ ammo, taking over the world.
A catalyst, I know, when I say go, put your hands up!
混沌の最中に
In the midst of chaos,
降臨した女神
the goddess has descended.
I freeze it up, got it ice cold on my body
You wanna know but you don't
震撼させる異能
A supernatural power that shakes the world
I'mma go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine, shine
Won't stop 煌めく my fantasy, now you see
Won't stop shining, my fantasy, now you see
星空を 濃ん染まるんだ 私色に
The starry sky will be dyed deeply in my colors
Hidden deep within my universe
Come find me now
Hear the voice that's calling out
まだ見ぬ世界の本質を見せてあげるから
I'll show you the true essence of a world yet unseen, so...
Baby, for now, calm down, let me focus
Under my spell like gnosis
So don't get too close when I'm
(Come-a, come-a) Comin' through, you wanna roll with me
(Come-a, come-a) Comin' through, we take 'em down, yes
I tell you what to do, I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do, 脳髄まで bulletproof
I tell you what to do, bulletproof down to my brain stem
Cold when I do, what I do, when I focus
Back at my best, I finesse
私の脳裏に潜む 怪物 is no secret
The monster lurking in my mind is no secret
冷静に cool, my attitude
Calm and cool, my attitude
Uh-uh, target in my sight, locked in, ready to shoot, like
Mayday, this is an emergency
Working under pressure, baby, I can do this in my sleep
世の理だって書き換えてしまうような頭脳
A mind capable of rewriting even the laws of the universe
When I go, when I go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine, shine
Won't stop 煌めく my fantasy, now you see
Won't stop shining, my fantasy, now you see
銀河を 音色を響かすように
Making the melodies resound across the galaxy
Hidden deep within my universe
Come find me now
Clear my mind of all these doubts
まだ見ぬ世界の本質をこの目で見たいから
'Cause I want to see the true essence of an unseen world with my own eyes
Baby, for now, calm down, let me focus
Under my spell like gnosis
So don't get too close when I'm
(Come-a, come-a) Comin' through, you wanna roll with me
(Come-a, come-a) Comin' through, we take 'em down, yes
I tell you what to do, I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do, 脳髄まで bulletproof
I tell you what to do, bulletproof down to my brain stem
Cold when I do, what I do, when I focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, oh
垂れる頭, don't break my focus
Bowing heads, don't break my focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, oh
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
I'mma get you talkin' 'bout it loud, can't get rid of me now
唯一無二 so I'm crowned, put my feet on the ground
One and only, so I'm crowned, put my feet on the ground
まぁ任せといてくわ, A piece of cake, it's no stress
Just leave it to me, a piece of cake, it's no stress
銀河中を魅了して, what's next? Take a guess
Captivating the whole galaxy, what's next? Take a guess
Yes, I tell you what to do, I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do, 脳髄まで bulletproof
I tell you what to do, bulletproof down to my brain stem
Cold when I do, what I do, when I focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, oh
垂れる頭, don't break my focus
Bowing heads, don't break my focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, oh
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
Focus!
DARK ARIA
The time has come
to pack away all the joys
You don't wanna hear my apology
Get it off my chest, I would do my best
I know what you fear, similarities
we possess
Never will I pass the test
The scene is fading
Can my soul be put to rest?
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales
Far from this tragedy?
Sad you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels' wings lifting and setting me free
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales
Far from this tragedy?
Sad you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels' wings lifting and setting me free
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
Woo! Aw, we're getting towards the end of the live.
There were so many beautiful songs, and so many beautiful guests!
I love the glasses, the KarisumaX and Dice-k glasses. Good stuff!
Ah, and we're getting to the end, which means announcements! Yeah!
Oh, but first off, after this live, there will be a members-only part as well, so join the NeFi family today!
えっと、この後もね、メン限パートもあるので、ぜひメンバーシップに入ってこい！
Um, after this, there's also a members-only section, so definitely join the membership!
歌、歌うんでね。 Yes!
I'll be singing, after all. Yes!
Ah, okay then! Are you guys ready for the announcement?
っすごくすごく嬉しい告知があります！
I have a super, super happy announcement to make!
There's a big announcement I'm really happy about! I can't wait! I'm super happy I get to share it with you guys!
はい！ 嬉しい告知いきます！
Alright! Here comes the happy announcement!
まずは、こちらをご覧ください！ Please watch this short video!
First, please take a look at this! Please watch this short video!
願いを叶える魔法があるとするなら
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes...
それは、あなた。
...it would be you.
2026.10.06
October 6, 2026
JAPAN TOKYO
Tokyo, Japan
IRyS 1st Concert
VENUE SGC HALL ARIAKE
そしてわたしは、あなたに贈る
And I will gift to you...
奇跡で出来た、この希望を。
...this hope made of miracles.
というわけで！ Yes!
So that's why! Yes!
IRyS, I will be having my very first solo live! Yay!
in Tokyo, Japan!
はい、というわけで、初めてのソロライブ、日本で開催されることが決定しました！
Yes, so my very first solo live has been confirmed to be held in Japan!
Yes! It will be in Tokyo at the SGC Hall Ariake!
えっと、場所は東京のSGCホール有明でございます！
Um, the venue is SGC Hall Ariake in Tokyo!
日程は10月6日！
The date is October 6th!
It's gonna be on a Tuesday. はい、火曜日でございますね。
It's gonna be on a Tuesday. Yes, it's a Tuesday.
It'll be happening on October 6th, Tuesday! Yeah!
Mark your calendars! カレンダーに書いておいや！
Mark your calendars! Write it down on your calendars!
ずっとね、本当に夢に見ていたステージに立てること、すごく嬉しく思いますし...
I'm so truly happy to stand on the stage I've always dreamed of...
本当にみんなの応援のおかげです、ありがとうございます！
...and it's all thanks to everyone's support, thank you so much!
It's all thanks to your guys's support that I get to have this opportunity, so thank you so much!
for your support until now! 頑張るぞー！ イエーイ！
for your support until now! I'll do my best! Yay!
えっとね、I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one for you guys, a very magical one!
Um, I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one for you guys, a very magical one!
So please look forward to it, make sure you definitely come!
If you don't come, I'll be sad. If you don't come, you'll also regret it! Yes!
あの、ライブに向けて準備めちゃくちゃ頑張ってるんで...
Um, I'm working super hard preparing for the live...
素晴らしいライブになるように頑張ってるんで、ぜひ会場へ見に来てください！
...and striving to make it a wonderful live, so please do come see it at the venue!
見に行かないとIRyS悲しいし、みんなも後悔するぞ！ はい！
If you don't come see it, IRyS will be sad, and you'll regret it too! Yes!
そして、あの、along with it, yes! I will also be releasing my very first full album! Woohoo!
And along with it, yes! I will also be releasing my very first full album! Woohoo!
なんと、IRyS初のフルアルバム出ます！
Surprisingly, IRyS's very first full album is coming out!
そう、なんだかんだ言ってね、今までEPだったんですけど、フルアルバムは初めてです！
Yeah, truth be told, I've released EPs until now, but this is my first full album!
Yeah, I've released EPs in the past, but this is the very first full album!
So look forward to it, there's a lot of songs! The album jacket...
よいしょ！ 見える？
Heave-ho! Can you see it?
Yeah, album jacket is by Kidokorota-sensei! Very cute!
The album title is called "DANGERUS"! Yes!
何でもリスをつければいいってもんじゃないかもしれないけど...
It might not be as simple as adding "RYS" to everything, but...
ちょうどハマったんでね、"DANGERUS"な、とっても危険的でホットなアルバムになってます！ Yes!
...it fit perfectly, so it's a "DANGERUS" and very dangerously hot album! Yes!
えっと、there are many songs written by all sorts of songwriters from all over the world!
Um, there are many songs written by all sorts of songwriters from all over the world!
...and there's going to be a lot of Eurobeat songs, but also songs that are not Eurobeat as well.
New genres as well, so I hope you guys look forward to that!
ね、あの国内外の様々なクリエイターに
Also, various creators from Japan and abroad...
ユーロビート以外の楽曲も多数作ってもらってます。
...have crafted many songs outside of Eurobeat for this album as well.
A lot of new songs!
えーっと、And I will be performing, of course, performing one of the songs for you today!
Um, and I will be performing, of course, performing one of the songs for you today!
今日もね、あの、1曲披露しようかなと思ってます！Showcase! Yay!
Today, I'm thinking of showcasing one of those songs as well! Showcase, yay!
The song I'll be showcasing for you today was written and arranged by...
...the Eurobeat circle SOUND HOLIC-san! Woohoo!
...the Eurobeat circle SOUND HOLIC! Woohoo!
Yes, they're very famous for Eurobeat songs, so I'm really glad, I'm really happy to be able to work with them. Thank you so much!
えーっとね、今回のお披露目する楽曲は
The song I'm showcasing today...
作曲・編曲、国内のユーロビートが得意とするクリエイターさん、SOUND HOLICさんでございます！ありがとうございます！
...was composed and arranged by SOUND HOLIC, creators known for their Eurobeat music in Japan! Thank you so much!
新たなユーロビートの見せ方になると思うんで、楽しみにしてて！
I think it offers a fresh take on Eurobeat, so please look forward to it!
It's Eurobeat, but there's something about it that's also not very Eurobeat, so I hope you guys know what I mean when I sing it! Yes!
Um, the digital release will be happening on 12 AM JST, upcoming 12 AM JST after this! So make sure you stream it on Spotify and other streaming services! Yeah!
Um, the digital release will be happening at 12 AM JST, upcoming 12 AM JST after this! So make sure you stream it on Spotify and other streaming services! Yeah!
この後ね、えーっと、デジタルリリースも各配信サイトで行われます。えーっと、0時に配信されます！楽しみにしててね！
After this, the digital release will be available on various streaming platforms. It will drop at midnight! Look forward to it!
すごいド派手な曲です！楽しみだ！
It's a super flashy song! I'm so excited!
Um, and as for the details of the album, I will be talking about that at the very end of this live, so be sure to stick till the end!
アルバムの詳細は、この後最後のほうでね、えーっと、いろいろ説明するんで、最後まで見てね！
I'll explain all the album details towards the end of the stream, so stay tuned until the very end!
All right then, please listen to my new song, "BE MY FLAME"! 新しい曲聴いてください、「BE MY FLAME」！
All right then, please listen to my new song, "BE MY FLAME"! Please check out my new song, "BE MY FLAME"!
Can't control it
anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
(Tension rising to the top,
Won't look back, I'll never stop,
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot
It's your fault, baby)
Fever burning up inside, It can't be contained
Got my heart going up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
(Come on and come on I wanna confess, baby oh baby I'm gettin' obsessed)
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
(Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, gonna be wanna be ready for more)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love
(And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up,
can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, It's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul,
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play: A dangerous game,
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
(Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash, breakin' me shakin' me makin' me crash)
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
(Drivin' me drivin' me drivin' me crazy, tellin' me tellin' me what do you mean)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love
(And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
I'm only getting started...
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you burning for me!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
So, how did you guys like my Birthday 3D Live?
We had so much going on from the new 3D outfit reveal,
new merch,
to my 1st album announcement,
solo live announcement,
and new song performances!
I think it was packed with so much, so...
I'd like to give you guys a recap and share the details.
ライブ本編、どうでしたか？
How was the main stream?
色々ね、告知盛りだくさんだったと思うので
We had a ton of announcements, so
改めておさらいと詳細をお伝えします。
I'd like to go over them again and share the details.
まずはグッズから！ First up, the merch!
First off, the merch!
We have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS illustrated by Inuno Niske-sensei,
the ChibiRyS Tote Bag illustrated by Lian-sensei,
the Race QueenRyS Keychain, which is a really cute race queen plushie keychain,
and the YabaiRyS Pouch!
For full set bonuses, the limited edition includes a postcard
with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped autograph.
The standard version includes a postcard with both a foil-stamped message and autograph.
And sales will start at 1:15 PM, which is like real soon if not maybe even now.
フルセットを買っていただいた方には
For those who purchase the full set,
数量限定版は直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます。
the limited edition comes with a postcard featuring a handwritten message and foil-stamped signature copy.
通常バージョンは箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りポストカードになります。
The standard version comes with a postcard featuring a foil-stamped signature copy and message.
この後1時15分にカートオープンするよ！
The cart will open after this at 1:15!
もうすぐだよ！
It's coming up very soon!
続いてアルバムです！ Next up, the album!
Next up, the album!
This time it's being released in two formats:
the CD and vinyl! Woo-hoo!
Pre-orders will begin also at 1:15 PM JST at the hololive production official shop, like real soon.
As for digital releases, that will happen on July 12th!
今回はCDとレコードの2種類のリリースとなっておりまして、
This time, it's being released in two formats: CD and vinyl record,
この後1時15分よりホロライブオフィシャルショップにて予約が開始されます！
and pre-orders will begin on the hololive official shop starting at 1:15!
デジタルリリースは7月12日です！
The digital release is July 12th!
CDにはここでしか聴けない「Gravity」のリアレンジバージョンとステッカー2種類、
The CD includes a rearranged version of "Gravity" available only here, plus 2 types of stickers,
レコードにはジャケットとアナザージャケットが印刷されたLPサイズ両面ポスターカードがついてきます。
while the vinyl record comes with an LP-sized double-sided poster card featuring both the jacket and alternate jacket art.
ポストカードじゃないよ、ポスターカード！
It's not a "postcard", it's a poster card!
もっとでかいです！
It's much bigger!
さらにこちらのポスターカードには両面のどちらかに必ず直筆サインが入ります！
Furthermore, on one side of this poster card, there will definitely be a handwritten signature!
サインされる面はランダムでございます！
The signed side will be random!
裏面かもしれないし、表面かもしれないです。
It might be on the back, or it might be on the front.
The CD will include an exclusive rearranged version of "Gravity" and two types of stickers,
while the vinyl comes with a double-sided LP-sized poster card.
Yes, a pretty darn big poster card, featuring both the main and alternate album covers.
Plus—yes, a big plus—
one side of this poster card will definitely feature a handwritten autograph!
The signed side will be random, so it could be on either the alternate jacket side or the main album cover!
We'll see when you get it!
And "Be My Flame", which was performed in today's 3D Live, will also be digitally released at midnight today! So don't forget to check it out!
そしてライブでお披露目した「Be My Flame」は24時にデジタルリリースもあるので、忘れずにチェックしてね！
And "Be My Flame", which was premiered during the live, will also be digitally released at midnight, so make sure to check it out!
And there's more! That's right!
My first solo live concert! Woo-hoo!
Tokyo at SGC Hall Ariake, woo!
And it will be held on a Tuesday on October 6th.
I'm super super duper excited for this,
and I'm so glad I got to finally announce it!
So I hope you guys will be really excited for it as well! Yay!
あとね、ソロライブも決まりました！
Also, my solo live concert has been confirmed!
場所は東京SGCホール有明でございます！
The venue will be SGC Hall Ariake in Tokyo!
えーっと、開催される日程は10月6日火曜日です！
Um, the date it will be held is Tuesday, October 6th!
すっごく楽しみにしてるし、
I'm really looking forward to it,
もうとにかく、もうこんなライブがやれる機会自体が本当にまさかできると思ってなくて、
and anyways, I never thought I'd get the chance to hold a concert like this,
とってもワクワクしてますし、これからも準備頑張ります！
so I'm super excited, and I'll keep doing my best to prepare!
Please look forward to further details and information in the future!
Last but not least, there will be a members-only part starting at 1:30 PM
pretty soon, so please come check it out if you can and join the family!
最後に、メン限定パートが1時半から始まるので、良かったらメンバーに入って見に来てね！
Lastly, the members-only stream starts at 1:30, so if you'd like, join as a member and come watch!
では、ありがとうございました！
Well then, thank you so much!
Thank you very much! Bye-ryS for now, until the members part!